In school you learn things by trying solutions several times-
-and by finding new ones.
It is impossible to do everything right right away.
It's not exciting either.
When the teacher assesses the quality of your school work, the knowledge requirements are used.
The knowledge requirements can be found in the curriculum that controls the teaching.
In crafts, image and technology, one must systematically try and rethink.
In craft, it is about how materials and techniques can be combined.
You should formulate different action alternatives that lead the work forward.
You are constantly thinking about new solutions.
A student has been given the task of manufacturing some kind of storage.
The material should be reusable.
The object should be created with flat technology.
That task can be solved in many different ways.